<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TECH-ANDGAR</title><link>https://tech-andgar.me/</link><description>Recent content on TECH-ANDGAR</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tech-andgar.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Talks</title><link>https://tech-andgar.me/talks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tech-andgar.me/talks/</guid><description>1: In-person seminar Google I/O Extended 2024 - Bogotá: Flutter y Dart: Empoderando el Desarrollo de Aplicaciones como Nunca Antes (00:31:41) [Colombian Sign Language (LSC) with Spanish Voice-over &amp;amp; with Subtitules automatic in others languages] Tag: Flutter Dart Web Development Mobile Development Date: 2024-07-27&amp;nbsp;-&amp;nbsp; Location: Bogotá D.C., Colombia&amp;nbsp;-&amp;nbsp; Channel YT: GDG Bogotá 2: Webinar : Ready to Write Clean, Dive into SOLID with Signers! (Part I &amp;amp; II - &amp;#39;SO&amp;#39;) (00:36:30) [International Sign Language (ISL) - Without Audio] Tag: SOLID Single Responsibility Principle SRP Open-Closed Principle OCP Software Engineering Date: 2024-06-19&amp;nbsp;-&amp;nbsp; Location: Virtual&amp;nbsp;-&amp;nbsp; Channel YT: Sign Language Tech 3: Webinar : Let’s discuss how to get prompted from Software Engineer to Senior Software Engineer (00:43:38) [International Sign Language (ISL) - Without Audio] Tag: Software Engineering Software Engineer Junior Senior Date: 2024-06-15&amp;nbsp;-&amp;nbsp; Location: Virtual&amp;nbsp;-&amp;nbsp; Channel YT: TECH-ANDGAR &amp;nbsp;-&amp;nbsp;Speakers Invitation: Milad Vafaeifard 4: Webinar : Flutter and Dart Empowering App Development like Never Before (00:54:05) [International Sign Language (ISL) - Without Audio] Tag: Flutter Dart Web Development Mobile Development Date: 2024-05-17&amp;nbsp;-&amp;nbsp; Location: Virtual&amp;nbsp;-&amp;nbsp; Channel YT: Space Codingx Video modified - Original Video in Channel: Space Codingx 5: Essay : ¿Cómo se escucha el silencio?</description></item><item><title>`http_status` Dart Package: A Comprehensive Guide</title><link>https://tech-andgar.me/posts/dart-http_status-package/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tech-andgar.me/posts/dart-http_status-package/</guid><description>http_status Dart Package: A Comprehensive Guide Link to heading Description Link to heading Constants: http_status provides convenient static constants representing all HTTP status codes defined in RFC 1945 (HTTP/1.0), RFC 2616 (HTTP/1.1), and RFC 2518 (WebDAV). Clarity: Each constant offers a clear name (e.g., ok, notFound, forbidden), making it easy to understand the meaning of a status code at a glance. Information: Constants also provide a concise description of the status code, which can be helpful in debugging or understanding API responses.</description></item><item><title>Dart - Use late allocation if possible</title><link>https://tech-andgar.me/posts/dart-late-keyword/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tech-andgar.me/posts/dart-late-keyword/</guid><description>Dart v2.9 added the late modifier on variables.
When Null Safety is enabled, it is sometimes necessary to explicitly state that we will initialize a non-null variable later. Dart cannot always assume that a variable will be initialized later, as in the case of high-level variables. The following example would throw an error in Dart.
This can be used in the following two cases.
Late assign: promise to assign later</description></item><item><title>Flutter Test Coverage</title><link>https://tech-andgar.me/posts/flutter-test-coverage/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tech-andgar.me/posts/flutter-test-coverage/</guid><description>LCOV is a graphical tool for GCC coverage testing with gcov. It creates HTML pages containing source code annotated with coverage information by collecting gcov data from multiple source files. LCOV supports &amp;ldquo;Line Coverage&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Function Coverage&amp;rdquo; measurement.
The LCOV report looks as follows:
Installation Link to heading Install on Ubuntu Link to heading sudo apt-get update -qq -y sudo apt-get install lcov -y Install on Mac Link to heading brew install lcov Install on Windows Link to heading Required:</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://tech-andgar.me/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tech-andgar.me/about/</guid><description>Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Andres Garcia, a Deaf Developer with over 5 years of experience, whose native language is Colombian Sign Language (Lengua de Señas Colombiana, LSC). I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about exploring the intersection of technology, logic, and communication to create innovative digital solutions.
My expertise spans:
• Mobile development: Flutter, Dart
• Web technologies: ES6+, HTML5, CSS3, Vue.js, TypeScript
• Back-end development: Node.js,Express, Loopback, Nest, RESTful APIs, GraphQL
• DevOps practices: CI/CD, Docker, microservices architectures</description></item><item><title>Cofiguration server</title><link>https://tech-andgar.me/posts/notes-config-server/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tech-andgar.me/posts/notes-config-server/</guid><description>View logs ngnix Link to heading $ cat /var/log/nginx/error.log # OR $ sudo tail -n 20 /var/log/nginx/error.log Check configuration nginx Link to heading $ nginx -c /etc/nginx/nginx.conf -t Reset service nginx on Ubuntu Link to heading $ sudo systemctl restart nginx Reload configuration of service nginx on Ubuntu Link to heading $ sudo systemctl reload nginx Assign permissitions for user of nginx on Ubuntu Link to heading $ chown -R www-data:www-data /var/www/domain.</description></item><item><title>Fix Error 15517 MS SQL SERVER</title><link>https://tech-andgar.me/posts/fix-error-ms-sql-server/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tech-andgar.me/posts/fix-error-ms-sql-server/</guid><description>Fix Error 15517 MS SQL SERVER
Original link
This particular snippet of code that is used to change the owner of a database in Microsoft SQL Server, is using a system stored procedure called sp_changedbowner to perform the action.
USE [DB Name] GO EXEC dbo.sp_changedbowner @loginame = N&amp;#39;sa&amp;#39;, @map = false GO Here&amp;rsquo;s the breakdown of what each line does:
USE [DB Name]: This command switches the current database to the specified database.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://tech-andgar.me/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tech-andgar.me/contact/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s connect! I&amp;rsquo;m happy to answer your questions, discuss potential projects, or simply chat about technology.
You can reach me at
H E L L O @ T E C H - A N D G A R . M E
Or by scheduling a call using the calendar below:
Schedule time with me Follow me on social media:</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://tech-andgar.me/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tech-andgar.me/projects/</guid><description>TRUSTED BY [ YOUR BRAND HERE ] [ YOUR BRAND HERE ] [ YOUR BRAND HERE ] ENDORSEMENTS FROM CONNECTIONS Thanks to your patience and active support, we managed to fix the code errors to support Vietnamese translation despite the challenges of communicating with international sign l...‏anguage. Your ability to prioritize and address problems efficiently was crucial in overcoming these challenges. I highly recommend your services for anyone seeking reliable and dedicated support in complex technical issues.</description></item></channel></rss>