<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TECH-ANDGAR</title><link>https://tech-andgar.me/</link><description>Recent content on TECH-ANDGAR</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tech-andgar.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>`http_status` Dart Package: A Comprehensive Guide</title><link>https://tech-andgar.me/posts/dart-http_status-package/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tech-andgar.me/posts/dart-http_status-package/</guid><description>http_status Dart Package: A Comprehensive Guide Link to heading Description Link to heading Constants: http_status provides convenient static constants representing all HTTP status codes defined in RFC 1945 (HTTP/1.0), RFC 2616 (HTTP/1.1), and RFC 2518 (WebDAV). Clarity: Each constant offers a clear name (e.g., ok, notFound, forbidden), making it easy to understand the meaning of a status code at a glance. Information: Constants also provide a concise description of the status code, which can be helpful in debugging or understanding API responses.</description></item><item><title>Dart - Use late allocation if possible</title><link>https://tech-andgar.me/posts/dart-late-keyword/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tech-andgar.me/posts/dart-late-keyword/</guid><description>Dart v2.9 added the late modifier on variables.
When Null Safety is enabled, it is sometimes necessary to explicitly state that we will initialize a non-null variable later. Dart cannot always assume that a variable will be initialized later, as in the case of high-level variables. The following example would throw an error in Dart.
This can be used in the following two cases.
Late assign: promise to assign later</description></item><item><title>Flutter Test Coverage</title><link>https://tech-andgar.me/posts/flutter-test-coverage/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tech-andgar.me/posts/flutter-test-coverage/</guid><description>LCOV is a graphical tool for GCC coverage testing with gcov. It creates HTML pages containing source code annotated with coverage information by collecting gcov data from multiple source files. LCOV supports &amp;ldquo;Line Coverage&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Function Coverage&amp;rdquo; measurement.
The LCOV report looks as follows:
Installation Link to heading Install on Ubuntu Link to heading sudo apt-get update -qq -y sudo apt-get install lcov -y Install on Mac Link to heading brew install lcov Install on Windows Link to heading Required:</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://tech-andgar.me/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tech-andgar.me/about/</guid><description>Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Andres, a Deaf developer whose native language is Colombian Sign Language (LSC). I have a passion for working with computers, whether it&amp;rsquo;s researching new software trends, learning new technologies, or exploring ways to integrate logic and communication.
Technologist specialized in application development for mobile devices with solid experience in mobile front-end in Flutter.
Technologist in Analysis and development in information systems with Front-end knowledge of HTML, CSS, Javascript, Vue.</description></item><item><title>Cofiguration server</title><link>https://tech-andgar.me/posts/notes-config-server/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tech-andgar.me/posts/notes-config-server/</guid><description>View logs ngnix Link to heading $ cat /var/log/nginx/error.log # OR $ sudo tail -n 20 /var/log/nginx/error.log Check configuration nginx Link to heading $ nginx -c /etc/nginx/nginx.conf -t Reset service nginx on Ubuntu Link to heading $ sudo systemctl restart nginx Reload configuration of service nginx on Ubuntu Link to heading $ sudo systemctl reload nginx Assign permissitions for user of nginx on Ubuntu Link to heading $ chown -R www-data:www-data /var/www/domain.</description></item><item><title>Fix Error 15517 MS SQL SERVER</title><link>https://tech-andgar.me/posts/fix-error-ms-sql-server/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tech-andgar.me/posts/fix-error-ms-sql-server/</guid><description>Fix Error 15517 MS SQL SERVER
Original link
This particular snippet of code that is used to change the owner of a database in Microsoft SQL Server, is using a system stored procedure called sp_changedbowner to perform the action.
USE [DB Name] GO EXEC dbo.sp_changedbowner @loginame = N&amp;#39;sa&amp;#39;, @map = false GO Here&amp;rsquo;s the breakdown of what each line does:
USE [DB Name]: This command switches the current database to the specified database.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://tech-andgar.me/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tech-andgar.me/contact/</guid><description>H E L L O @ T E C H - A N D G A R . M E</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://tech-andgar.me/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tech-andgar.me/projects/</guid><description>Side Projects Link to heading I&amp;rsquo;ve done a handful of side projects over the past few years. Here are some of the ones that I&amp;rsquo;m proud of.
14 Items of projects: 🗃️ Type 🎁 Project 🛠 Technologies Package Dart exception_handler A Dart package for streamlined API handling and robust exception management in Flutter apps. Flutter Dart GitHub Actions Coveralls App mobile clean-flutter-app (Source code) Application made in Flutter using TDD, Clean Architecture, Design Patterns and SOLID principles.</description></item></channel></rss>